# Theerawat Silimechok

(+66) 62-440-8169 · bankt21@gmail.com · linkedin portfolio



## **SUMMARY**

Experienced Electronics and Computer Technician with 3 years of experience, including 1 year as a System Integrator, currently seeking a Programmer position. Skilled in designing user-friendly interfaces, ensuring policy compliance, and solving problems effectively. Excited to apply analytical skills, work well in teams, and use Agile methods for success in programming and software development.

# **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Ract JavaScript C, Python Cloud Computing Data Visualization System Administrator

Device Configuration and Management IoT Technology

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### System Integrator Royal Thai Air Force

Sep 2022 - Sep 2023

Gather system requirements from the organization. Plan work to create a system so that the entire system Work is consistent and responds to the supervisor's policy. and use it to develop the system to make the organization more complete.

#### **Accomplishments:**

- Responsible for planning and maintaining the company's electronic and computer systems, including hardware and software, to ensure they are always new and up-to-date. Increase work speed by 40%
- Performance improvement and proper maintenance. Switch from Windows 7 operating system to Windows 10 and 11, and replace old devices with new ones. For example, the printer server has been optimized, with stable performance and equipment running 80% faster than before.
- Contact suppliers and other IT personnel to resolve issues, ensure uninterrupted work, and immediately improve work continuity. 24/7
- Training between the Royal Thai Air Force and the Malaysian Air Force, code AIR THAMAL 30/2022, in the position of Support of electronic equipment.

## **IT Support & Administrator**

Feb 2018 - Sep 2022

#### **Royal Thai Air Force**

Provide assistance in solving various problems regarding information technology systems so that they can be used normally.

## **Accomplishments:**

- Setting up and maintaining Windows user accounts and access management systems Implementing network and computer systems policies of 400 users
- Detect and troubleshoot software and hardware failures. Respond to an average of 25 user requests and software errors per day. On site and monitor troubleshooting
- Manage and maintain IT hardware and software inventory Prepare spare parts for 40 computers and electronic devices
- Install and configure computer software and systems such as Windows OS, Microsoft 365, Zoom, Team and office software, on average 10 computers per day.

# **EDUCATION**

# **Junior Software Developer Bootcamp**

Nov 2023 - Present

Generation Thailand & King Mongkut's University of Technology Thonburi

- Scrum Team or utilize Agile Methodology
- Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC) procedures with focused proficiency in development.
- front-end languages and libraries (e.g. HTML/ CSS, JavaScript, React, Boostrap, Web Responsive)
- back-end languages and libraries (e.g. SQL, MongoDB)

## **Electronics and Computer Technology**

2023

Phranakhon Rajabhat University

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S.) GPA 3.5

- Create a robot controlled by C language with Arduino program, make an IoT system, connect devices to control the smart farm house system.
- Participated in the competition of Artificial Intelligence Machinery, Nuclear Power Plant Thailand 4.0 Passed to the final round.
- participated in the MITSUBISHI ELECTRIC CUP AUTOMATION 2023 competition. Passed to the final round and ranked 9th out of 16 teams.